It's so hot!
天太热了
Ah... Aww. That breeze is nice!
啊 噢 这阵风真好
Ehh... It's lovely!
嗯 感觉真好
Look!
看
The storm is coming! We'd better go home.
暴风雨就要来了 我们最好回家去
Do we have to? I want to keep playing.
我们必须这样做吗 我想继续玩儿
We can come back after the storm.
暴风雨过后我们可以再回来
Big Nutbrown Hare, we found the most amazing tree.
大棕兔 我们发现了最神奇的树
It's our favorite tree.
是我们最喜欢的树
We climbed up like this,
我们这样爬上去
and then slip down it,
然后滑下来
like this.
像这样
Oh, that does sound like fun.
哦 听起来是很有趣
Oh, the flower! Is it sad?
噢 花 它很悲伤吗
It just needs water. It's a hot day.
它只是需要水 今天是个炎热的日子
And it's about to get a good drink now.
它就要好好喝个痛快了
Let's go and find somewhere to stay dry.
我们去找个干的地方待着吧